let animeQuestions = [
  {
    question : "How many Hasiahra are in Demon Slayer? ",
    correctAnswer : 2,
    choices : ["Twelve", 
               "Seven", 
               "Nine",
               "Eleven"]
  } , 

  {
    question : "Which anime make up the orginal Big 3?",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["DragonBall Z, Naruto, One Piece",
                "OnePiece, Nauto, Bleach",
                "Yu Yu Hakksho, DragonBall Z , Roushin Kenshin", 
                "Demon Slayer, My Hero Academia , Black Clover" ]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What is Ichigos Bankai called?" ,
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["Hakka No Togame",
               "Tensa Zangetsu",
               "Sōō Zabimaru",
               "Daiguren Hyōrinmaru"]
  } , 

  {
    question : "Deku wanted to be a hero because of what hero?",
    correctAnswer : 0,
    choices : ["All Might", 
              "Endeavor",
              "Eraserhead" , 
              "Gran Torino"]
  } ,
  
  {
    question : "What workout routine resulted in Saitama's incredible power?",
    correctAnswer : 3,
    choices : ["100 squats , burpees, toe-taps, 20 km jog", 
              "100 sit-ups , toe-taps, supermans, 10 km jog",
              "100 pull-ups , push-ups, lunges, 2 hours jumping rope", 
              "100 sit-ups , push-ups, squats, 10 km jog" ]
  } , 

  {
    question : "What was the phrase Vash the Stampede based his actions from?",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["Whatever happens,happens", 
               "Love and peace",
               "If you don’t take risks, you can’t create a future!", 
               "Sometimes it’s necessary to do unnecessary things."]
  },

  {
    question : "Which wall in Attack on Titan was destoryed first",
    correctAnswer : 3,
    choices : ["Wall Maria", 
               "Wall Sina", 
               "Wall Rose", 
               "Wall Luna"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "How many dragon balls do you need to grant a wish",
    correctAnswer : 0,
    choices : ["Seven", 
               "Four", 
               "Ten", 
               "Eight"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "Besides water whatelse can ghouls consume?",
    correctAnswer : 1,
    choices : ["Soda",
               "Coffee",
               "Wine",
               "Milk"]
  } ,

  {
    question : "What fighting style does Mori Jin use in God of highschool?",
    correctAnswer : 0,
    choices : ["Renewal Taekwondo",
               "Tai Chi",        
               "Northern ITF Taekwondo",
               "Full Contact Karate"]
  } ,


]

export {
  animeQuestions 
}